BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/022 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm
1941-1946
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics
6178/022 mf
35.56 cubic feet
320 microfilm reels
Collective bargaining argreements, microfilm.
8036796
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 30, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21). Digital
UUnited States Department of Labor; Bureau of Labor Statistics
8036796
- A1 Actors and Artistes of America, Associated; A4 Air Line Pilots Ass'n International; A5 Architects and Draftsmen's Union International Federation of Technical Engineers (Reel 1)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America 1941 (62 contrs.) (Reel 2)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America 1942-1943 (Reel 3)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America 1943-1944 (Reel 4)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America 1944 (Reel 5)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America 1944-1945 (Reel 6)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America 1945 (Reel 7)
- United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Workers of America 1945 (Reel 8)
- A9 Automobile Workers of America, United (AFL) 1941-45 (Reel 9)
- A9 Automobile Workers (cont.); B 2 Barbers and Beauty Culturists Union of America (CIO) 1942; B 3 Barbers etc. (AFL) 1942 (Reel 10)
- B3 Barbers (AFL) cont.; B 4 Bill Posters, Billers & Distributors (AFL) 1942; B 5 Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers & Helpers (AFL) 1942 (Reel 11)
- B5 Blacksmiths etc (cont.) 1942-45 (Reel 12)
- B6 Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders and Helpers of America (AFL) 1941-45 (Reel 13)
- B9 Brick & Clay Workers of America (AFL) 1941-43; B 10 Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers (AFL) 1941-43; B 11 Bridge and Structural Iron Workers (AFL) 1941-43 (Reel 14)
- B11 Bridge & Structural, etc (cont) 1944; B12 Broadcast Engineers (Ind) 1944; B 13 Broom and Whisk Makers Union (AFL) 1944; B 14 Building Service Employees (AFL) (Reel 15)
- B14 Building Service (cont) 1945; B 15 Building Trades (AFL) 1945; C 1 Carpenters & Joiners of America (AFL) 1941 (Reel 16)
- C1 Carpenters & Jointer (cont) 1941-43 (Reel 17)
- C1 Carpenters & Joiners (cont.) 1943-1945 (Reel 18)
- C1 Carpenters and Joiners (cont.) 1945; C 2 Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers (AFL) 1942 (Reel 19)
- C2 Cement, Lime etc. (cont.) 1942-44 (Reel 20)
- C2 Cement, Lime etc. 9cont. 1944; C3 Chemical Workers Union (AFL) 1942 (Reel 21)
- C3 Chemical Workers Union (cont.) 1942-44 (Reel 22)
- C3 Chemical Workers (cont.) 1944; C 4 Cigar Makers International Union (AFL) 1944-45; C 5 Cleaning and Dye House Workers (AFL) 1945 (Reel 23)
- Clothing Workers of America, Amalgamated (CIO) 1941-43 (Reel 24)
- C6-43-33 thru 09-41-18 (Reel 25)
- C9 Coopers International Union (AFL) cont.; D1 Diamond Workers' Protective Union (AFL); D 2 Die Sinkers Conference (Ind); D3 Distillery, Rectifying and Wine Workers (AFL) (Reel 26)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (CIO) 1941 (Reel 27)
- E1 Electrical Radio and Machine Workers etc. (CIO) 1941-42 (Reel 28)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers etc. (CIO) 1942 (Reel 29)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and machine Workers etc. (CIO) 1942-1943 (Reel 30)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (CIO) 1943 (Reel 31)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, (CIO) 1943 (Reel 32)
- E1 Electrical Radio and Machine Workers 1943-44 (Reel 33)
- E1 Electrical Radio and Machine Workers 1944-45 (Reel 34)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers 1945 (Reel 35)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers 1945 (Reel 36)
- E1 Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers 1945 (Reel 37)
- E2 Electrical Workers 1942 (Reel 38)
- E2 Electrical Workers 1942-43 (Reel 39)
- E2 Electrical Workers 1943-44 (Reel 40)
- E2 Electrical Workers 1944 (Reel 41)
- E2 Electrical Workers 1944-45 (Reel 42)
- E2 Electrical Workers 1945 (Reel 43)
- E2 Electrical Workers 1945 (Reel 44)
- E4 Engineers, Int'l Union of Operating 1941-42 (Reel 45)
- E4 Engineers, Int'l Union of Operating 1943-44-45 (Reel 46)
- E4 Engineers, Int'l Union of Operating 1945 (Reel 47)
- Union Contracts; F1 Farm Equipment and Mental Workers 1941-1945; F4 Firefighters 1944 (Reel 48)
- F5 Firemen and Oilers 1941-45 (Reel 49)
- F6 Fisherman and Allied Workers 1943-45; F7 Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Allied Workers 1941-1943 (Reel 50)
- F7 Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Allied Workers 1944-45 (Reel 51)
- F7 Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Allied Workers 1945 (Reel 52)
- F10 Furniture Workers of America 1941-44 (Reel 53)
- F10 Furniture Workers of America 1944-45 (Reel 54)
- G1 Garment Workers of America. 1941-45 (Reel 55)
- G2 Garment Workers Union, Int'l Ladies 1941 (Reel 56)
- G2 Garment Workers' Union, Int'l Ladies 1941-45 (Reel 57)
- G2 Garment Workers' Union, Int'l Ladies 1945 (Reel 58)
- G3 Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers 1943-45 (Reel 59)
- G4 Class Bottle Blowers 1941-43 (Reel 60)
- G4 Glass Bottle Blowers 1943-45 (Reel 61)
- G5 Glass, Ceramic and Silica Sand Workers 1941-45 (Reel 62)
- G7 Glass Workers Union, 1941-1945 (Reel 63)
- G8 Glove Workers Union of America 1941-1945 (Reel 64)
- G11 Granite Cutters' Int'l Assn. of America 1941-45 (Reel 65)
- H1 Hatters and Millinery Workers 1941-45 (Reel 66)
- H2 Hod Carriers' Suilding and Common Laborers' 1942-45 (Reel 67)
- H4 hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders 1941 (Reel 68)
- H4 Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders 1941 (Reel 69)
- H4 Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders 1942 (Reel 70)
- H4 Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders 1943-45 (Reel 71)
- Jewelry Workers 1941-45 (Reel 72)
- L3 Laundry Workers 1941-42 (Reel 73)
- L3 Leather Workers 1943-45 (Reel 74)
- L4 Leather Workers Int'l Union 1942-45 (Reel 75)
- L5 Leather Workers Union, (Fur and) 1941 (Reel 76)
- L5 Leather Workers Union, (Fur and) 1941-44 (Reel 77)
- L5 Leather Workers Union, (Fur and) 1944-45 (Reel 78)
- L14 Longshoremen's Ass'n Int'l 1942-1945 (Reel 79)
- L15 Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Int'l 1941-1945 (Reel 80)
- L16 Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers Union, Int'l (Handbag and ) 1941-45 (Reel 81)
- M2 Machinists, Int'l, Ass'n. of 1941-42 (Reel 82)
- M2 Machinists, Int'l, Ass'n. of 1942-43 (Reel 83)
- M2 Machinists, Int'l. Ass'n. of 1943 (Reel 84)
- M2 Machinists, Int'l. Ass'n of 1943-44 (Reel 85)
- M2 machinists, Int'l. Ass'n of 1944-45 (Reel 86)
- M2 Machinists, int'l. Assn; of 1945 (Reel 87)
- M2 machinists, Int'l Assn' of 1945 (Reel 88)
- M2 machinists, Int'l Assn' of 1946 (Reel 89)
- M3 Maintenance of Way Employers 1943-45; M4 marble, Slate, and Stone Polishers, Rubbers, etc. 1942-44; M8 Marine and Shipbuilding Workers 1941-44 (Reel 90)
- M8 marine and Shipbuilding Workers 1944-45 (Reel 91)
- M9 Maritime Union of America 1943-45 M11 Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen 1941 (Reel 92)
- M11 Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen 1941-42 (Reel 93)
- M11 Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen 1942 (Reel 94)
- M11 Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen 1943 (Reel 95)
- M11 Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen 1944 (Reel 96)
- M11 Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen 1945 (Reel 97)
- M12 Mechanics Educational Society 1941-45 (Reel 98)
- M17 Metal Trades 1941-44 (Reel 99)
- M17 Metal Trades 1945 (Reel 100)
- M15 Metal Engravers and Marking Device Workers 1941-45; M16 Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers 1941 (Reel 101)
- M16 Metal polishers, Buffers, Platers and Helpers 1941-45 (Reel 102)
- M19 Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers 1941 (Reel 103)
- M19 Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers 1941-42 (Reel 104)
- M19 Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers 1943-44 (Reel 105)
- M19 Line, Mill and Smelter Workers 1944-1945 (Reel 106)
- M19 Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers 1945 (Reel 107)
- D-M-19 Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers. (Die Casting). 1941 (Reel 108)
- MD19 Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers (Die Casters) 1942 (Reel 109)
- M21A Mine Workers and America, District 50 1941-1942 (Reel 110)
- M21A Mine Workers of America District 50 1942-43 (Reel 111)
- M21A Mine Workers of America District 50 1943 (Reel 112)
- M21A Mine Workers of America District 50 1944 (Reel 113)
- M21A Mine Workers of America District 50 1944-45 (Reel 114)
- M21A Mine Workers of America District 50 1942 (Reel 115)
- M21A Mine Workers of Am. District 50 1945; M21B United Construction Workers 1942-45 (Reel 116)
- M21B United Construction Workers 1945 (Reel 117)
- M21 Mine Workers of America 1941 (Reel 118)
- M21 Mine Workers of America 1941 (Reel 119)
- M21 Mine Workers of America 1942-45 (Reel 120)
- M21 Mine Workers of America 1945 (Reel 121)
- M22 Molders and Foundry Workers 1941-43 (Reel 122)
- M22 Molders and Foundry Workers 1943-44 (Reel 123)
- Molders and Foundry Workers 1944-45 (Reel 124)
- M23 Musicians, Am. Federation of 1941-43 (Reel 125)
- M23 Musicians, Am. Federation of 1943-45 (Reel 126)
- N1 Newspaper, Guilds, Am. 1941-45 (Reel 127)
- N1 Newspaper Guild, Am. 1945 (Reel 128)
- O1 Office Employees 1942-45 (Reel 129)
- 02 Office and Professional Workers 1941-44 (Reel 130)
- 02 Office and Professional Workers 1944; A02 Office and Professional Workers (Architects, Engineers, Chemists etc.) 1945 (Reel 131)
- 03 Workers Int'l Union 1941 (Reel 132)
- 03 Workers Int'l Union 1941-43 (Reel 133)
- 03 Oil Workers Int'l Union 1943-44 (Reel 134)
- 03 Oil Workers Int'l Union 1944-45 (Reel 135)
- 03 Oil Workers Int'l Union 1945 (Reel 136)
- P1 Packinghouse Workers of America 1941 (Reel 137)
- P1 Packinghouse Workers of America 1941-44 (Reel 138)
- P1 Packinghouse Workers of America 1944-45 (Reel 139)
- P2 Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers 1942 (Reel 140)
- P2 Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers 1943-45 (Reel 141)
- P3 Paper Makers 1941-42 (Reel 142)
- P3 Paper Makers 1942-45 (Reel 143)
- P3 Paper Makers 1945 (Reel 144)
- P4P10Paper, Novelty and Toy Workers 1941-42 (Reel 145)
- P4P10 Paper, Novelty, and Toy Workers 1942-43 (Reel 146)
- P4 Paperworkers of America 1944-45 (Reel 147)
- P5 Pattern Makers' League of North Am. 1941-45 (Reel 148)
- P6 Paving Cutters' Union 1941-45 (Reel 149)
- P7 Hhoto-Engravres' Union 1941 (Reel 150)
- P7 Photo-Engravers' Union 1941-42 (Reel 151)
- P10 Playthings, Jewelry and novelty Workers 1944-45 (Reel 152)
- P11 Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry 1941-45 (Reel 153)
- P19 Potters, Nati'l Brotherhood 1941-45 (Reel 154)
- P20 Printing Pressmen and Assistants 1941 (Reel 155)
- P20 Printing Pressmen and Assistants 1942-45 (Reel 156)
- P21 Public Workers of America 1942-44 (Reel 157)
- P22 Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1941-42 (Reel 158)
- P22 Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers 1942-45 (Reel 159)
- P22 Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers 1945 (Reel 160)
- R4 Railroad Trainmen, Bro. of 1941-45 (Reel 161)
- R11 Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, etc. 1944-45 (Reel 162)
- R14 Retail Clerks 1941-42 (Reel 163)
- R14 Retail Clerks 1942-44 (Reel 164)
- R14 Retail Clerks 1944-45 (Reel 165)
- R15 Retail, Wholesale, and Dept. Store Union 1941-43 (Reel 166)
- R15 Retail, Wholesale and Dept. Store Union 1943-45 (Reel 167)
- R15 Retail, Wholesale and Dept. Store Union 1945 (Reel 168)
- R17 Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers 1941-43 (Reel 169)
- R17 Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers 1943-44 (Reel 170)
- R17 Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers 1944-45 (Reel 171)
- R17 Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers 1945 (Reel 172)
- S2 Seafarers' Int'l Union 1942-1945 (Reel 173)
- S4 Sheet Metal Workers' 1941-1943 (Reel 174)
- S4 Sheet Metal Workers' 1943-45 (Reel 175)
- S7 Shoe Workers Union, Boot and 1941-45 (Reel 176)
- S8 Shoe Workers of America, United 1941-45 (Reel 177)
- S14 Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators 1941 (Reel 178)
- S14 Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators 1941-42 (Reel 179)
- S14 Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators 1942-45 (Reel 180)
- S15 State, County and Municipal Employees 1942-45 (Reel 181)
- AS16 Aluminum Workers of America 1942-45; S16 Steelworkers of America 1941 (Reel 182)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1941 (Reel 183)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1941-42 (Reel 184)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1942 (Reel 185)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1942 (Reel 186)
- S16 Stelworkers of America 1943 (Reel 187)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1943 (Reel 188)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1944 (Reel 189)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1944 (Reel 190)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1944 (Reel 191)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1944 (Reel 192)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1945 (Reel 193)
- S16 Steelworkers of America 1945 (Reel 194)
- S18 Stone and Allied Products Workers 1941-45 (Reel 195)
- S20 Stove Mounters Int'l Union 1941-45 (Reel 196)
- S21 Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America 1941 (Reel 197)
- S21 Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America 1941 (Reel 198)
- Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America 1941-45 (Reel 199)
- S21 Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America 1945 (Reel 200)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers 1941 (Reel 201)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers 1941 (Reel 202)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers 1941 (Reel 203)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers 1941 (Reel 204)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers 1942 (Reel 205)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen and Helpers 1942 (Reel 206)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers 1942-43 (Reel 207)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen and Helpers 1944-45 (Reel 208)
- T2 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers 1945 (Reel 209)
- T3 Telegraphers Union, Commercial 1941-45 (Reel 210)
- T4 Telephone Workers Ind. 1941-45 (Reel 211)
- T5 Textile Workers of America 1941-43 (Reel 212)
- T5 Textile Workers of America 1943-45 (Reel 213)
- T6A Textile Workers Union (Dryers) 1941-45 (Reel 214)
- T6B Textile Workers Union (Hosiery) 1941-45 (Reel 215)
- T6 Textile Workers Union 1941 (Reel 216)
- T6 Textile Workers Union 1941-42 (Reel 217)
- T6 Textile Workers Union of America 1942-43 (Reel 218)
- T6 Textile Workers Union of America 1944 (Reel 219)
- T6 Textile Workers Union of America 1945 (Reel 220)
- T6 Textile Workers Union of America 1945 (Reel 221)
- T7 Tobacco Workers Int'l Union 1941-1945 (Reel 222)
- T11 Transport Workers Union 1941-45 (Reel 223)
- U1 Upholders' Int'l Union 1941 (Reel 224)
- U1 Upholders' Int'l Union 1941-45 (Reel 225)
- U1 Upholders' Int'l Union 1945 (Reel 226)
- U2 Utility Workers Union of America 1941-45 (Reel 227)
- W6 Woodworkers of America 1941-45; W3 Welders of America 1945; W4 Wire Weavers' Protective Assn' 1942-43 (Reel 228)
- FLU- Grain Processors 1941-1943-63 (Reel 229)
- Federal Labor Union- Grain Processors 1943-1944 (38) (Reel 230)
- FLU-Aluminum Council 1941-45; FLU Match Council 1942-45; Railway Patrolmen 1944-45; Railway Carmen of America 1943-45 RR and Steamship Clerks, etc. 1941-43 (Reel 231)
- Federal Labor Union 1941 (Reel 232)
- Federal Labor Union 1941-42 (Reel 233)
- Federal Labor Union 1942-43 (Reel 234)
- Federal Labor Union 1943 (Reel 235)
- Federal Labor Union 1943-44 (Reel 236)
- Federal Labor Union 1944-45 (Reel 237)
- Federal Labor Union 1945 (Reel 238)
- Local Industrial Union 1942-44 (Reel 239)
- Local Industrial Union 1944-45 (Reel 240)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1941-42 (Reel 241)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1942 (Reel 242)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1942 (Reel 243)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1942 (Reel 244)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1942-43 (Reel 245)
- Unaffiliated unions 1943 (Reel 246)
- Unaffiliated unions 1943-44 (Reel 247)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1944 (Reel 248)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1944 (Reel 249)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1944-45 (Reel 250)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1945 (Reel 251)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1945 (Reel 252)
- Unaffiliated Unions 1945 (Reel 253)
- Miscellaneous 1 through 30 (Reel 254)
- Miscellaneous 31 through 148 (Reel 255)
- Miscellaneous 149 through 158 (Reel 256)
- Miscellaneous 159 through 227 (Reel 257)
- Miscellaneous 228 through 272 (Reel 258)
- Non-Manufacturing Industry 1947 Airlines through Maritime Industry (Reel 259)
- Non-manufacturing Industry 1947; Motion pictures-Services (Reel 260)
- Non-manufacturing Industry- 1947; Services through end of Non-manufacturing Industries (Reel 261)
- Apparel through Food (Reel 262)
- Manufacturing Industries- 1947; Food through Special Industry Machinery (Reel 263)
- Manufacturing Industries-1947; Special Industry Machinery through Revere Copper and Brass Col., Rome, NY (Reel 264)
- Manufacturing Industries 1947; Primary Smelting and Refining (Non-Ferrous Metals) through Transportation Equipment (Sullivan Dry Dock and Repair) (Reel 265)
- Transportation Equipment -Todd Shipbuilding and Repair (Reel 266)
- Non-manufacturing Industries - 1946 Airlines (Reel 267)
- Non-manufacturing industries- 1946 Building Construction through Personal Services (Reel 268)
- Non-manufacturing Industries- 1946; Social Services through End of Non-manufacturing industries (Reel 269)
- Apparel through Chemicals and Allied Products (Reel 270)
- Manufacturing Industries- 1946; Chemicals through Wire Products (Iron and Steel) (Reel 271)
- Manufacturing Industries- 1946 Wire Products (Iron and Steel) through Miscellaneous Industries (Reel 272)
- Manufacturing Industries 1946; Miscellaneous Industries through Commercial Job Printing (Reel 273)
- Union Contracts; Manufacturing Industries, 1946; Commercial Job Printing trough end of Manufacturing Industries (Reel 274)
- Key Co.: KA-1 through KA-25 (Reel 275)
- Key Co.: KA-26 through KA-55-3-43 (Reel 276)
- Key Co.: KA-55-3-44 through KA-77-43 (Reel 277)
- Key Co.: KA-77-43 through KA-99 (Reel 278)
- Key Co.: KB-1 through KB-14-42 (Reel 279)
- Key Co.: KB-14-44 through KB-53 (Reel 280)
- Key Co.: KB-54 through KB-76 (Reel 281)
- Key Co.: KC-1 through KC-11 (Reel 282)
- Key Co.: KC-12 through KC-51-42 (Reel 283)
- Key Co.: KC-51-45 through KC-100 (Reel 284)
- Key Co.: KC-101 through KC-122 (Reel 285)
- Key Co.: KD-1 through KD-13-42 (Reel 286)
- Key Co.: KD-13-44 through KD-37 (Reel 287)
- Key Co.: KE-1 through KE-21-42 (Reel 288)
- Key Co.: KE-21-43 through KF-36 (Reel 289)
- Key Co.: KF-37 through KF-40 (Reel 290)
- Key Co.: KG-1 through KG-16-1 (Reel 291)
- Key Co.: KG-16-2 through KG-45-40 (Reel 292)
- Key Co.: KG-45-40 through KH-37-42 (Reel 293)
- Key Co.: KH-37-43 through KI-19-2-38 (Reel 294)
- Key Co.; KI-19-2-39 through K-K-5 (Reel 295)
- Key Co.: KL-1 through KM-5 (Reel 296)
- Key Co.: KM-6 through KM-39-42 (Reel 297)
- Key Co.: KM-39-44 through KM-69 (Reel 298)
- Key Co.: KM-70 through KM-74 (Reel 299)
- Key Co.: KN-1 through KN-13 (Reel 300)
- Key Co.: KN-14 through KN-46-41 (Reel 301)
- Key Co.: KN-46-43 through KN-63 (Reel 302)
- Key Co.: K0-1 through K0-3-46 (Reel 303)
- Key Co.: K0-3-46 through K0-18 (Reel 304)
- Key Co.: KP-1 through KP-6-1-45 (Reel 305)
- Key Co.: KP-6-1-45 through KP-26 (Reel 306)
- Key Co.: KP-27 through KP-62 (Reel 307)
- Key Co.: KQ-1 through KR-39 (Reel 308)
- Key Co.; KS-1 through KS-7-39 (Reel 309)
- Key Co.: KS-7-40 through KS-38 (Reel 310)
- Key Co.: KS-39 through KS-60-47 (Reel 311)
- Key Co.: KS-60-47 through KS-94 (Reel 312)
- Key Co.: KT-1 through KT-16-41 (Reel 313)
- Key Co.: KT-16-42 through KT-28 (Reel 314)
- Key Co.: KU-1 through KU-19-1-43 (Reel 315)
- Key Co.; KU-19-1-44 through KV-9 (Reel 316)
- Key Co.: KW-1 through KW-7- 41 (Reel 317)
- Key Co.: KW-7-44 through KW-44 (Reel 318)
- Key Co.: KW-45 through KW-61-2 (Reel 319)
- Key Co.: KY-1 through KXA-24 (Reel 320)